[CO2.Earth
---------

](https://www.co2.earth/)

----------------------------------------

#### CO2.Earth Website Service  
Privacy Policy  

Last updated: March 18, 2022

This website with URL [https://www.co2.earth](http://co2.earth/) is owned and operated by Pro Oxygen.  The term ‘Pro Oxygen’ or ‘us’ or ‘our’ or ‘we’ refers to Pro Oxygen, the owner of the website and operator of the website service.

This privacy policy was prepared for users of the CO2.Earth website service ("Service"). The policy describes how ProOxygen collects, uses, protects and manages personal identifiable information ("PII") of users of the Service.  PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate an individual.

When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when:

* you register on our site
* subscribe to a newsletter
* volunteer to help with a CO2.Earth project or activity
* make donations

What personal information do we collect from visitors?

The following basic information may be collected when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter, volunteer, or make a donation:

* Name
* email address
* Phone number and/or Skype username (when volunteering)
* Physical address (when volunteering)
* Resume or informaton about your interests and experiences (when volunteering)

If you make a donation, personal and financial information is collected and processed by PayPal at a webpage protected with an SSL certificate.   Payment and information collection is subject to the PayPal privacy policy ([https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)).  PayPal forwards donations and basic personal identifying inforation to ProOxygen (name, address and email). 

How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you in a way that is consistent with the context when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

* To personalize or enhance your experience at the site
* To send periodic newsletters you subscribe to
* To respond to questions or other communications you initiate
* To manage website registrations and blog comments
* To maintain ongoing communications for collaborating or coordinating work or projects related to CO2.Earth

CAN SPAM Act

To comply with CANSPAM requirements we agree to the following:

* NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
* NOT use advertising in messages
* Include our address in messages
* Monitor third party email services for compliance
* Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email
* Promptly remove users from our lists in response to requests to opt-out or unsubscribe

Registration Information

Newsletter subscribers and site registrants may view and change personal information they submitted online.

How do we protect visitor information?

* Information stored on CO2.Earth is restricted to Pro Oxygen representatives who have signed a privacy and confidentiality undertakingrequire and use the infortmation for Pro Oxygen purposes permissable under this policy
* Information kept offsite by ProOxygen is stored on a password-protected storage device
* Credit card information is not collected or accessed by Pro Oxygen

Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. See the Pro Oxygen [cookies policy](https://www.co2.earth/cookies) for this site.

Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to third parties.

Third party links

We do not include or offer third-party commercial products or services on our site.

Advertising

We do not sell or display advertising at CO2.Earth.

Analytics

This site uses Google Analytics to collect non-personal demographic and aggregate statistics to monitor site usage.  The use of this statistical information is subject to the Google Analytics Terms of Service ([http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html)).

Anonymous Visits

We allow anoymous visitors at the CO2.Earth site.

We honour Do Not Track (DNT) signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a DNT browser mechanism is in place.

Third party behavioral tracking

We do not allow third party behavioral tracking.

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

CO2.Earth does not specifically market to children under 13.

Fair Information Practices Principles

In accordance with Fair Information Practices Principles, we will take the following responsive action should a data breach occur:

* We will notify affected users by email within 7 business days.

Contact  

If there are questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us.

Pro Oxygen  
1516 Winchester Road  
Victoria   British Columbia  V8N 2B5  
Canada

Email:    This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.

Phone:  1.778.535.6760

### Languages

Select LanguageEnglishAfrikaansShqipአማርኛالعربيةՀայերենAzərbaycan diliEuskaraБеларуская моваবাংলাBosanskiБългарскиCatalàCebuanoChichewa简体中文繁體中文CorsuHrvatskiČeština‎DanskNederlandsEsperantoEestiFilipinoSuomiFrançaisFryskGalegoქართულიDeutschΕλληνικάગુજરાતીKreyol ayisyenHarshen HausaŌlelo Hawaiʻiעִבְרִיתहिन्दीHmongMagyarÍslenskaIgboBahasa IndonesiaGaeligeItaliano日本語Basa Jawaಕನ್ನಡҚазақ тіліភាសាខ្មែរ한국어كوردی‎КыргызчаພາສາລາວLatinLatviešu valodaLietuvių kalbaМакедонски јазикMalagasyBahasa MelayuമലയാളംMalteseTe Reo MāoriमराठीМонголဗမာစာनेपालीNorsk bokmålپښتوفارسیPolskiPortuguêsਪੰਜਾਬੀRomânăРусскийSamoanGàidhligСрпски језикSesothoShonaسنڌيසිංහලSlovenčinaSlovenščinaAfsoomaaliEspañolBasa SundaKiswahiliSvenskaТоҷикӣதமிழ்తెలుగుไทยTürkçeУкраїнськаاردوO‘zbekchaTiếng ViệtCymraegisiXhosaיידישYorùbáZulu

### Search

Box Label    

### Twitter

### Features

### Facebook

### Newsletter

### A Trend To End

### Vital Signs

####   

### 2021 Glasgow Climate Conference

_**The world cannot stabilize what it does not watch.  
**_

Copyright © 2007 - 2024 Pro Oxygen.  Some Rights Reserved.  
CO2.Earth is an independent, citizen-led initiative.
